7th Sense Media - Privacy Policy   

PRIVACY POLICY
==============

Updated as of May 30th, 2024

7th Sense Media Ltd (“7th Sense Media” “we” or “us”), a Seychelles company, has established this Privacy Policy to explain how we may collect, retain, process, share and transfer your Personal data when you use our Software, and our Services, and to allow you to make an informed decision about how you will use our Services.

Our "Services" include the Software on this website, the services provided thereon, and all related services, applications, components, programs, software, listings, directories, tools, updates, databases and information made available and utilized. References to "you" or “user” in this Agreement means you, your duly authorized representatives and any entity you may represent in connection with your use of the Services.

This Privacy Policy addresses only our practices with respect to information we collect in the course of using our Services and does not apply to information about you that might be collected by a third-party website or an offering linked to or otherwise accessible from our Services. Any information collected, obtained and/or used by any such third parties is subject to the privacy policies of those third parties. We encourage you to review the policies of such third parties.

What Information Do We Collect?
-------------------------------

7th Sense Media may collect information about you when you visit our Sites or use our Services, including the following:  

1. Information you provide us  
    We collect the content, communications and other information you provide when you contact us, including your email address.  

2. Information we get from your use of our services  
    We collect information about the Services that you use and how you use them. This information includes:  
      
    * Search activity when you use web search services (such as search queries) (“Search Data”).
    * Internet protocol address (“IP Address”)
    * The type of browser you are using when using our Services, including your browser's "user agent" (e.g., Chrome, Firefox, Edge, Internet Explorer, Safari, and other browsers)
    * Device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser language, and the date and time of your request and referral URL
    * Your geographic location
    * The Domain name of your Internet service provider
    * The source of traffic acquisition
    * Date of traffic acquisition, and
    * Time and date of certain browser events such as:
    
    * Chrome extensions enabled
    * Homepage/new tab rendered
    * Search query performed
    * Search performed on search engine results page (“SERP”)
    * Search term on SERP
    * Paid advertisements clicked on SERP
    * Organic advertisements clicked on SERP
    * Icons clicked on Home page/New Tab Page
    * Uninstalls of extension
    * Views on landing page
    * Clicks on an action button on landing page
    * Cancellations of extension installation
    * Acceptance of extension installation
    * Disablement of extension

* Device Information  
    We collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model and operating system version).  

* Log Information  
    When you use our Services or view content provided by 7th Sense Media , we automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This includes:  

How Do We Use This Information?  

----------------------------------

We are able to deliver, personalize, and improve our Services by combining and using the information that we have about you to understand how you use and interact with our Services. We also may use the information that we have about you for the following purposes:  

* Provide, maintain, improve, and develop relevant features, content, and Services.  

* To communicate with you by responding to your requests, comments, and questions.  

* Help advertisers and publishers connect to offer relevant advertising in their apps and websites.  

* Create analytics and reports for internal purposes. These analytics and reports may include aggregate or anonymous information.  

* Detect and defend against fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful activity.  

How Do We Share This Information?
---------------------------------

We will not share the personal information we collect about you with any third party for their own marketing purposes without your consent. We do not sell, license or share information that individually identifies our users with companies, organizations or individuals outside of 7th Sense Media . We will share your information in the following ways:  

* Our vendors, subcontractors and business partners (“service providers”): We may share your data with our services providers who process your personal data to provide services to us or on our behalf. We have contracts with our service providers that prohibit them from sharing the information about you that they collect or that we provide to them with anyone else or using it for other purposes.  

* Companies within 7th Sense Media ’s group of companies: We may share your information with our parent company and our affiliates, which are entities under common ownership or control of our ultimate parent company.  

* Fraud prevention: We may disclose the personal information we collect about our users when we believe disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or respond to suspected illegal or fraudulent activity or to protect the safety, rights, or property of us, our users, or others.  

* Law enforcement purposes and public safety: If requested or required by government authorities, such as law enforcement authorities, courts, or regulators, or otherwise to comply with the law, we may disclose any information we have about our users. We may disclose information collected about you in order to exercise or protect legal rights or defend against legal claims. We also may be required to disclose an individual’s personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.  

* Sale or merger of our business: We may transfer your personal information to a third party if we or any of our affiliates are involved in a corporate restructuring (e.g., a sale, merger, or other transfer of assets).  

* Advertisers and advertising networks: Advertisers and advertising networks place ads (including sponsored links in search results) on our site. These companies may collect information, such as your computer’s IP address, browser information, and search queries, as you use our Site and Services. They also may use cookies and other technologies to collect this information when you visit our site as described below.

How Do We Use Cookies and Tracking Technology?
----------------------------------------------

We use cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, and similar files or technologies to collect and store the information we automatically collect about your computer, device, and product usage. We use the term "cookies" in this policy to refer to cookies and all such similar technologies that collect information automatically when you are using 7th Sense Media ’s Services. 

How Long Do We Keep the Information?
------------------------------------

We retain the information we collect about and from you for as long as necessary to fulfill a business purpose or comply with a legal request. We may also choose to anonymize certain information you provide to us so that it can no longer be attributed to you if we would like to retain it for longer periods of time.

How Do We Protect Your Personal data?
-------------------------------------

We maintain technical, physical, and administrative security measures designed to provide reasonable protection for your personal data against loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, and alteration. The security measures include firewalls, data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, and information access authorization controls. While we are dedicated to securing our systems and Services, you are responsible for securing and maintaining the privacy of your password(s).

Age Limitations
---------------

The Sites and Services are not directed to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information, including personal data, from children or other individuals who are not legally able to use our Sites and Services. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal data from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly delete it, unless we are legally obligated to retain such data. Contact us if you believe that we have mistakenly or unintentionally collected information from a child under the age of 13.

International Data Transfers
----------------------------

7th Sense Media may transfer your personal data to countries other than the one in which you live. In particular, your personal data will be transferred to and processed in the United States where many of our central databases operate. By using the Services, you acknowledge that the data protection and other laws of other countries, such as the United States, may provide a less comprehensive or protective standard of protection than those in your country, and consent to your personal data being collected, processed and transferred as set forth in this Privacy Policy and US law. 7th Sense Media offers European Union Model Clauses, also known as Standard Contractual Clauses, to meet the adequacy and security requirements for our users that operate in the European Union.

Your Rights
-----------

Individuals located in certain countries, including the European Economic Area, have certain statutory rights in relation to their personal data. Subject to any exemptions provided by law, you may have the right to request access to personal data, as well as to seek to update, delete or correct this Information. If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact us. To the extent that 7th Sense Media ’s processing of your personal data is subject to the General Data Protection Regulation, 7th Sense Media relies on your consent. If we have collected and process your personal data with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time.

Data Protection Authority
-------------------------

Subject to applicable law, you also have the right to (i) restrict 7th Sense Media ’s use of your personal data and (ii) lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area and believe we maintain your Personal data within the scope of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you may direct questions or complaints to our lead supervisory authority.

More Information
----------------

For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit [http://www.netcoalition.com](http://www.netcoalition.com/) and [http://www.privacyalliance.org](http://www.privacyalliance.org/). In addition, the Federal Trade Commission Consumer Response Center offers a helpline at 1-877-FTC-HELP (1-877-382-4357) to allow consumers to make comments or inquiries regarding companies and business practices. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like access to personal information we may have about you in our files, to correct, update or to have us delete it, or if you would like to notify us of your choice to opt-out of any sharing of your personal information, please contact us at the address below.

Contact us at: info@7thsense.media  

7th Sense Media

1st Floor, Dekk House,

Zippora street, Providence Industrial Estate

Mahe

Republic of Seychelles

Tel: +230 464 2668

Terms of Service
================

Updated May 30th, 2024

We hope that you will enjoy the great features of our website and extension we provide (the "Services") as detailed below. These terms of use (the "Terms of Service") are a legal agreement between you and us setting forth, among other things, the terms and conditions for your access and use of the Services, the website, and any related sub-domains, which are operated by 7thSense Media (the "Website").

We reserve the right to change these Terms of Service from time to time without notice. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Terms of Service periodically to familiarize yourself with any modifications. Your continued use of our Services or this site after such modifications will constitute acknowledgment and agreement of the modified terms and conditions. If we make any substantial changes to the Terms of Service, we will post a notice on our home page along with a copy of the previous changes along with any substantial changes we made on this page.

Services Accessible
-------------------

The Services are intended for a general audience, and children and minors under the age of eighteen (18) are not permitted to access or use the Resources, absent express consent from their parents or guardians. We do not intentionally solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a minor under age 18, please contact us at: info@7thsense.media and we will remove it. If you are a parent or guardian who approves of your minor's use of the Services, please contact us and provide to us the age and email address of your minor on whose behalf you are contacting us.

In order to access our Customer Support, please contact us at: info@7thsense.media

Third Party Sites. The Website and the Services may contain links to third party sites or resources that are not owned or controlled by 7thSense Media. 7thSense Media has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, practices or availability of any third party sites or resources or the products, services or other materials on or available from such sites or resources. You are and remain subject to the policies of those third parties where applicable. By using the Website and the Services, you expressly relieve 7thSense Media from any and all liability (direct or indirect) arising from your use of any share functionality or third-party site or resource accessed from the Website or the Services. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to anyone. We reserve the right to change, modify or delete links to third party websites without notice.

Partners. 7thSense Media and/or its affiliated partners/associations/organizations which participate in the growth of the Services may present advertisements or promotional materials on or through the Website. Your dealings with, or participation in promotions of, any third-party advertisers on or through the Website are solely between you and such third party and your participation is subject to the terms and conditions associated with that advertisement or promotion. You agree that 7thSense Media is not responsible or liable for any loss or damage of any sort (direct or indirect) incurred as the result of any such dealings or as the result of the presence of such third party materials on the Website or made available through the Website. Reference to any products, services, processes, or other information, by trade name, trademark, manufacturer, supplier, or otherwise does not constitute or imply endorsement, sponsorship or recommendation thereof by 7thSense Media.

Service Interruptions
---------------------

Interruptions. You acknowledge that: (i) your access to and use of the Website and the provision Services may be suspended for the duration of any unanticipated or unscheduled downtime or unavailability of any portion or all of the Website or the Services for any reason, including as a result of power outages, system failures or other interruptions; and (ii) we shall also be entitled, without any liability to you, to suspend access to any portion or all of the Website or the Services at any time (a) for scheduled downtime to permit us to conduct maintenance or make modifications to any Service; (b) in the event of a denial of service attack or other attack on the Website or other event that we determine, in our sole discretion, that a risk to the applicable Service, to you or to any of our other users may be created if the Service were not suspended; or (c) in the event that we determine that any Service is prohibited by law or we otherwise determine that it is necessary or prudent to do so for legal or regulatory reasons (collectively, "Service Interruptions").

No Liability. 7thSense Media shall have no liability whatsoever for any damage, liabilities, losses (including any loss of data or profits) or any other consequences that you may incur as a result of any Service Interruption.

Notice of Interruption. To the extent we are able, we will endeavor to post updates on the Website regarding any Service Interruption and resumption of service following any such suspension, but shall have no liability for the manner in which we may do so or if we fail to do so.

Surviving Obligations. All provisions of the Terms of Service which by their nature should survive expiration or termination shall survive the expiration or termination of the Terms of Service, including, without limitation, ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers, and limitations of liability. Termination of your access to and use of the Website shall not relieve you of any obligations arising or accruing prior to such expiration or termination or limit any liability which you otherwise may have to 7thSense Media, including without limitation any indemnification obligations contained herein.

Intellectual Property
---------------------

Grant of License. 7thSense Media grants you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, worldwide, revocable license to access and use of the Website and the Services in accordance with the terms set forth in the Terms of Service. The Website and the Services are made available to you for your non-commercial use only. You need to obtain our permission if you want (i) to sell, distribute, license or in any other way exploit, in whole or in part, the Services (including by way of a bundle with other products and/or services) or any information or software associated with them or (ii) to modify or create derivative works from the Website in whole or in part.

Reservation of Rights. 7thSense Media reserves all right, title and interest not expressly granted under this license to the fullest extent possible under applicable laws. You may not sublicense, assign, or transfer the license granted to you under the Terms of Service, and any attempt to sublicense, assign, or transfer any part of your rights under the Terms of Service is void.

Trademarks and Copyright. The following are trademarks (registered or not) of 7thSense Media: "7thSense Media", as well as certain other 7thSense Media trademarks, service marks, graphics, and logos (collectively, the "Trademarks") used in connection with the Website and the provision of Services. The Website may also contain third-party trademarks, service marks, graphics, and logos, including with respect to products and/or services that may be purchased on our partners' websites (collectively, the "Other Trademarks").

Copyright. All content displayed on the Website as well as all the software (including any source code) used in connection with the Services is the exclusive property of 7thSense Media or third parties and is protected by copyright laws.

No License. Nothing appearing on the Website will be construed as granting you any license, right, title or interest relating to the Trademarks, the Other Trademarks or other intellectual property used in connection with the Website and the Services (collectively, the "Intellectual Property") and the Intellectual Property remains the exclusive property of 7thSense Media or owners. Except as stated herein, you agree not to display, copy, reproduce, use or distribute any Intellectual Property without our prior written consent. Also, you cannot mirror any material contained on the Website.

Feedback. If you choose to communicate suggestions for improvements to the Website or the Services (collectively, "Feedback"), we shall own all right, title, and interest in and to the Feedback and we shall be entitled to use the Feedback without restriction. You hereby irrevocably assign all right, title and interest in and to the Feedback to us and waive all you moral rights in the Feedback, and agree to provide us such assistance as we may require to document, perfect, and maintain our rights to the Feedback. You acknowledge and agree that: (i) your Feedback does not contain confidential or proprietary information; (ii) 7thSense Media is not under any obligation of confidentiality, express or implied, with respect to the Feedback; (iii) 7thSense Media shall be entitled to use or disclose (or choose not to use or disclose) such Feedback for any purpose, in any way, in any media worldwide; (iv) 7thSense Media may have something similar to the Feedback already under consideration or in development; and (v) you are not entitled to any compensation or reimbursement of any kind from 7thSense Media under any circumstances.

Copyrights/Trademarks
---------------------

All content and materials available on 7thSense Media, including but not limited to text, graphics, website name, code, images and logos are the intellectual property of 7thSense Media, and are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law. Any inappropriate use, including but not limited to the reproduction, distribution, display or transmission of any content on this site is strictly prohibited, unless specifically authorized by 7thSense Media.

Termination of Use
------------------

You agree that we may, at our sole discretion, suspend or terminate your access to all or part of our website and Resources with or without notice and for any reason, including, without limitation, breach of this User Agreement. Any suspected illegal, fraudulent or abusive activity may be grounds for terminating your relationship and may be referred to appropriate law enforcement authorities. Upon suspension or termination, your right to use the Resources we provide will immediately cease, and we reserve the right to remove or delete any information that you may have on file with us, including any account or login information.

Choice of Law and Venue
-----------------------

This Agreement shall be interpreted and enforced in all respects under the laws of Seychelles, as applicable to contracts to be performed entirely within the Seychelles. Any litigation arising out of this Agreement will be brought solely and exclusively in the state or federal courts located in the Seychelles, and the parties agree that jurisdiction and venue properly lie in such courts and waive any claim that a proceeding in any such court has been brought in an inconvenient forum. The United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods shall not apply to this Agreement.

No Guarantee
------------

UNLESS OTHERWISE EXPRESSED, 7thSense Media EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.

Privacy
-------

Your privacy is very important to us, which is why we've created a separate Privacy Policy in order to explain in detail how we collect, manage, process, secure, and store your private information. Our privacy policy is included under the scope and incorporated into this User Agreement. To read our privacy policy in its entirety, click here.

Miscellaneous
-------------

These Terms of Service along with any another notices, policies, procedures, and terms and conditions on our Site contain the entire understanding with respect to your use of our Site and our Services. You and we are independent contractors and nothing in these Terms of Service creates a partnership, joint venture, employment, or agency relationship. You may not assign these Terms of Service or any rights or obligations herein without our prior written consent and any such assignment or attempt thereat will be null and void. No purported waiver of any provision of these Terms of Service by us will be effective unless in a writing signed by us. If any provision of these Terms of Service for any reason shall be declared void, illegal, invalid, or unenforceable in whole or in part, such provision will be severable from all other provisions herein and will not affect or impair the validity or enforceability of any other provision of these Terms of Service; provided, however, that a court having jurisdiction may revise such provision to the extent necessary to make such provision valid and enforceable. The failure by us to enforce any provision of these Terms of Service will not be deemed a waiver of such provision or any other provision.

Disclaimers
-----------

"AS IS" BASIS. THE WEBSITE AND THE SERVICES (INCLUDING ALL THEIR CONTENT) ARE PROVIDED TO YOU "AS IS." THE USE OF THE WEBSITE AND THE SERVICES ARE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGES TO YOUR HARDWARE DEVICE OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE USE OF THE WEBSITE AND THE SERVICES. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, 7thSense Media DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, MERCHANTABLE QUALITY, DURABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON INFRINGEMENT. 7thSense Media MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES OR GUARANTEES THAT THE WEBSITE AND THE SERVICES WILL BE FREE FROM LOSS, DESTRUCTION, DAMAGE, CORRUPTION, ATTACK, VIRUSES, INTERFERENCE, HACKING, OR OTHER SECURITY INTRUSION, AND 7thSense Media DISCLAIMS ANY LIABILITY RELATING THERETO. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS MAY OR MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.

Warranty Disclaimer
-------------------

Your Information. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOUR SUBMISSION OF ANY INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. 7thSense Media DOES NOT ASSUME ANY LIABILITY TO YOU WITH REGARD TO ANY LOSS OR LIABILITY RELATING TO SUCH INFORMATION IN ANY WAY.

Third Party Content.
--------------------

SOME OF THE CONTENT DISPLAYED ON THE WEBSITE MAY INCLUDE MATERIALS THAT BELONG TO OR ARE PROVIDED BY THIRD PARTIES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO UCG). YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT 7thSense Media ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR SUCH CONTENT, PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES.

Copyright Materials ALL IMAGES, LINKS, AND VIDEOS THAT APPEAR ON ANY SITE OR SERVICE ("SERVICE"), OWNED AND OPERATED BY 7thSense Media (HEREAFTER "7thSense Media ", "WE", "OUR", OR "US"), ARE ASSUMED COPYRIGHTED BY THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS AND 7thSense Media CLAIMS NO CREDIT FOR THEM UNLESS OTHERWISE NOTED. IF YOU OWN THE RIGHTS TO ANY OF THE IMAGES, LINKS, OR VIDEOS AND DO NOT WISH THEM TO APPEAR ON THE SERVICE, PLEASE CONTACT US WITH THE INFORMATION REQUESTED IN THE SECTION "COPYRIGHT MATERIALS: NO UNAUTHORIZED USE" OF THESE TERMS OF SERVICE AND THEY WILL BE PROMPTLY REMOVED.

FURTHERMORE, NO CONTENT WITHIN OUR SERVICE (USER COMMENTS, RATINGS, PHOTOS, VIDEOS, LINKS, ETC.) REPRESENTS AN IMPLIED OR EXPRESS ENDORSEMENT OF ANY KIND BY ANY CELEBRITY, PERSON, USER, COMPANY, TEAM, LEAGUE, CHARITY, SCHOOL, STORE, OR ANY OTHER ENTITY REPRESENTED OR FEATURED ON THE SERVICE. ASSOCIATIONS OR CONNECTIONS ON THE SERVICE ARE FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY

Limitation of Liability & Indemnity
-----------------------------------

Limitation of Liability. IN NO CASE WILL 7thSense Media, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, SHAREHOLDERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, OR PARTNERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT,INDIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY, PUNITIVE DAMAGES OR OTHER DAMAGES, OR FOR ANY LOSSES, DAMAGES, LIABILITIES, COSTS AND EXPENSES ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO (I) YOUR USE, MISUSE OR INABILITY TO USE THE WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES, OR (II) THE INTERRUPTION, SUSPENSION OR TERMINATION OF ANY PART OF OR ALL THE WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES, OR (III) YOU RELIANCE PLACED BY YOU ON THE COMPLETNESS, ACCURACY OR EXISTING OF ANY ADVERTISING, OR AS A RESULT OF ANY RELATIONSHIP OR TRANSACTION BETWEEN YOU AND ANY ADVERTISER OR SPONSOR WHOSE ADVERTISING APPEARS ON THE WEBSITE, REGARDLESS OF THE CAUSE OF ACTION (WHETHER IN CONTRACT, WARRANTY, DELICT, QUASI-DELICT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER THEORY OF LIABILITY) AND EVEN IF 7thSense Media HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. NOTHWITHSTANDING ANYTHING TO THE CONTRARY IN THESE TERMS OF SERVICE, BECAUSE THE 7thSense Media SERVICE IS FREE, IN NO EVENT WILL 7thSense Media'S AGGREGATE LIABILITY FOR ANY CLAIMS IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE, AND THE SERVICES EXCEED US$1. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS MAY OR MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.

Indemnity. YOU WILL INDEMNIFY AND HOLD 7thSense Media, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, SHAREHOLDERS, AGENTS, LICENSORS AND EMPLOYEES HARMLESS WITH RESPECT TO ANY SUITS, CLAIMS OR DEMANDS (INCLUDING REASONABLE LAWYERS' FEES) ARISING OUT OF (I) YOUR BREACH OF THESE TERMS OF SERVICE; (II) ANY DAMAGES BY YOU OR YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE OR THE SERVICESCAUSED TO A THIRD PARTY; OR (III) YOUR USE OR MISUSE OF THE WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES.

General
-------

No Partnership. No agency, partnership, joint venture, or employment is created between you and 7thSense Media as a result of the Terms of Service and you do not have any authority of any kind to bind 7thSense Media in any respect whatsoever.

Search Engine
-------------

By clicking "Add to chrome", you accept and agree to installing the Karma Nature extension and setting Chrome New Tab search to that provided by the service. The search will be powered by Bing.

Contact Information
-------------------

If you have any questions or comments about these our Terms of Service as outlined above, you can contact us at: info@7thsense.media

Contact us at: info@7thsense.media  

7th Sense Media

1st Floor, Dekk House,

Zippora street, Providence Industrial Estate

Mahe

Republic of Seychelles

Tel: +230 464 2668

Contact Us
==========

Please also feel free to contact 7th Sense Media if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or 7th Sense Media ’s practices, or if you are seeking to exercise any of your statutory rights.  
Contact us at: info@7thsense.media  

7th Sense Media

1st Floor, Dekk House,

Zippora street, Providence Industrial Estate

Mahe

Republic of Seychelles

Tel: +230 464 2668

All rights reserved 7thSense Media 2020-2024
